<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Zed Zed Zed</name>
  <author>Johnny Berry / Vyberware</author>
  <packageId>vyberware.zedzedzed</packageId>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.6</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases</downloadUrl>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <description>
Zed Zed Zed is a RimWorld zombie mod built around slow pressure, bad nights, and colonies that never quite get to relax. Instead of relying on one repeated raid, the mod mixes together edge trickles, huddled packs, base pushes, ground bursts, grave events, moon attacks, and full herd crossings so the outbreak feels like it is always pressing somewhere.

The horde includes several strains with different jobs. Biters make up the bulk of the dead. Runts clog tight spaces. Boomers burst into acid. Sick zombies spread filth and infection. Drowned prefer water, rain, and wet conditions. Brutes hit harder. Grabbers pin pawns in place. Lurkers are the colony side oddball that can be captured, recruited, or enslaved.

Combat is tuned around fragile undead, not tanky ones. Every zombie belongs to the zombie faction, has no ideoligion, counts as a cannibal, ignores pain, filth, and nudity, shambles slowly unless it rolls the rare runner strain, doubles its movement speed at night, and swarms loud gunfire much harder than quiet melee.

The mod also adds zombie infection for living pawns, bile med kits, zombie bile surgery that can turn a patient into a colony lurker, zombie resources like rotten flesh, rotten leather, jerky, bile, and gold teeth, rotten leather furniture and floors, a themed settings menu, a pause menu shortcut, debug tools, custom naming, and a small HUD that shows current danger on your home map.

Built for RimWorld 1.6. Requires Harmony.
  </description>
</ModMetaData>
