<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Zed Zed Zed</name>
  <author>Johnny Berry / Vyberware</author>
  <packageId>vyberware.zedzedzed</packageId>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.6</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases</downloadUrl>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <description>
Zed Zed Zed is a RimWorld zombie mod built around slow pressure, ugly cleanup, and bad nights that can spiral out of control. Instead of throwing the same raid at you over and over, the mod mixes together edge trickles, huddled packs, base pushes, ground bursts, grave events, full moons, and blood moons. The result feels more like an outbreak that keeps wearing your colony down than a single attack you can clean up and forget.

The horde includes several strains with different jobs. Biters make up the bulk of the dead. Runts are smaller and nastier in tight spaces. Boomers burst into acid. Sick zombies spread infection, filth, and bile. Drowned zombies are strongest around water and roam more freely in rain. Brutes soak damage and hit hard. Grabbers pin pawns in place. Lurkers can show up as a rare passive strain you can capture, recruit, or enslave, while the other strains can be broken into colony slavery if you manage to capture them alive.

The mod also adds zombie infection and reanimation, craftable bile treatment kits, a medical bill that can inject zombie bile and turn a living patient into a colony lurker, zombie resources like rotten flesh, rotten leather, jerky, bile, and gold teeth, rotten leather furniture and floors, a themed settings menu, a pause menu shortcut to settings, debug tools, custom naming for the zombie family and each strain, prioritized double tapping job controls so selected workers can keep corpses down, and a small HUD readout that shows current danger on your home map.

Built for RimWorld 1.6. Requires Harmony.
  </description>
</ModMetaData>
