<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>Zed Zed Zed</name>
  <author>Johnny Berry / Vyberware</author>
  <packageId>vyberware.zedzedzed</packageId>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.6</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>brrainz.harmony</packageId>
      <displayName>Harmony</displayName>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/pardeike/HarmonyRimWorld/releases</downloadUrl>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/2009463077</steamWorkshopUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <description>
Zed Zed Zed is a RimWorld zombie mod built around slow pressure, bad nights, and colonies that never quite get to relax. Instead of relying on one repeated raid, the mod mixes together edge trickles, huddled packs, base pushes, ground bursts, grave events, moon attacks, and full herd crossings so the outbreak feels like it is always pressing somewhere.

The horde includes several strains with clear roles. Biters push the main pressure. Bone Biters peel off to feed on corpses. Runts clog tight paths. Boomers want crowded prey and bad spacing. Sick zombies spread filth and infection. Drowned want water, rain, and wet ground. Brutes try to break through in close melee. Grabbers lock prey in place. Lurkers are the colony side exception that prefers quiet base life over open hostility.

Combat is tuned around fragile undead, not tanky ones. Hostile zombies belong to the zombie faction. Zombies have no ideoligion, count as cannibals, ignore pain, filth, and nudity, shamble slowly unless they roll the rare runner strain, double their movement speed at night, and swarm loud gunfire much harder than quiet melee. Lurkers stay as the friendly exception.

The mod also adds zombie infection for living pawns, bile med kits, zombie bile surgery that can turn a patient into a colony lurker, zombie resources like rotten flesh, rotten leather, jerky, bile, and gold teeth, rotten leather furniture and floors, a themed settings menu, a pause menu shortcut, debug tools, custom naming, and a small HUD that shows current danger on your home map.

Built for RimWorld 1.6. Requires Harmony.
  </description>
</ModMetaData>
